<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>일기 on My English</title>
    <link>https://nofailed.github.io/blog/diary/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 일기 on My English</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ko-kr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 20:59:25 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nofailed.github.io/blog/diary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>20201126</title>
      <link>https://nofailed.github.io/blog/diary/20201126/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 11:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nofailed.github.io/blog/diary/20201126/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m free today because my family except me have gone to my parents-in-law&amp;rsquo;s house which is placed in Daegu city today to take part in making Kimchi would happen. Even I getting free time, it&amp;rsquo;s hard to utilize on weekdays, especially if it came unexpectedly like today. In addition, I&amp;rsquo;ve just arrived home from my company and what I want now is just sleeping. I&amp;rsquo;m too tired to do something even I&amp;rsquo;m writing this now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20201026</title>
      <link>https://nofailed.github.io/blog/diary/20201026/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 11:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nofailed.github.io/blog/diary/20201026/</guid>
      <description>Very frustrating day today is. I made a big mistake today. Everything I had been doing became a nothing today. Yesterday I took a train to go to my mother&amp;rsquo;s house in Daegu to stay a night because I had to take a physical ability test to become a police officer at Daegu.
The test consisted of two kinds of running. The first one was a 100-meter run and the second was a 1-kilometer run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20201009</title>
      <link>https://nofailed.github.io/blog/diary/20201009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2020 11:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nofailed.github.io/blog/diary/20201009/</guid>
      <description>Challenge for being a police officer #2 Continuing from the last diary about my challenge for becoming a police officer, I passed the practical test of the certificate. This means that eventually, I&amp;rsquo;m qualified to apply for the job posting of a police officer. Though qualified with the EIP certificate, I also needed to take more tests to get extra points which will be helpful for the competition of career recruitment because I had nothing to get the additional points until that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20200923</title>
      <link>https://nofailed.github.io/blog/diary/20200923/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 11:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nofailed.github.io/blog/diary/20200923/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve never had dreamed to become a police officer before. But there were some events that made me to challenge becoming police officer.
When I made my mind, the plan of the state examination to the police officer this year was not yet opened until that time. Even though having no information, I could assume what I&amp;rsquo;m needed with the recruitment notice from maritime police which had been anounced in advance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20200808</title>
      <link>https://nofailed.github.io/blog/diary/20200811/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 09:09:26 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nofailed.github.io/blog/diary/20200811/</guid>
      <description>check list    grammar example try     1형식 The dog sleeps on the sofa . I got up early this morning even there weren&amp;rsquo;t any responsibilities that belonged to me.   2형식 - 상태 He is a firefighter. I was totally free since I was alone.   2형식 - 변화 Paul became the president. I became single only for today or some days more If my family doesn&amp;rsquo;t come back soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://nofailed.github.io/blog/diary/20210119/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nofailed.github.io/blog/diary/20210119/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m in pain nowadays especially on the right side of my shoulder. For some months right after the failure of practical test for the job recruiting of a police officer, I&amp;rsquo;d stopped to work out. One day, about a month later from the stopping, I started to feel pain in my shoulder when I woke up in the morning. At that moment, I just thought the pain would be released as time goes by because around that time I was in a stopped state to exercise for a while and there was no reason that makes the pain.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
